Christine Brown has a good job, a great boyfriend, and a bright
future. But in three days, she's going to hell.
Drag Me to Hell is a horror, thriller film directed by Sam Raimi.
After denying a woman the extension she needs to keep her home, loan officer Christine
Brown sees her once-promising life take a startling turn for the worse.
Christine is convinced she's been cursed by a
Gypsy, but her boyfriend is skeptical.
Her only hope seems to lie in a psychic who claims he can help her lift the
curse and keep her soul from being dragged straight to hell.
Christine Brown, played by Alison Lohman.
Clay Dalton, played by Justin Long.
Mrs. Ganush, played by Lorna Raver.
Rham Jas, played by Dileep Rao.
Mr. Jacks, played by David Paymer.
Shaun San Dena, played by Adriana Barraza.
Drag Me to Hell is a 2009 American supernatural horror tragedy film directed and co-written by Sam Raimi with Ivan
Raimi, starring Alison Lohman, Justin Long, Lorna Raver, Dileep Rao, David Paymer, and Adriana Barraza.
The story focuses on a loan officer who, in an effort to prove to her boss that she can make
the "hard decisions" at work, chooses not to extend an elderly woman's mortgage.
The old woman places a retaliatory curse on her that, after three days of escalating
torment, will plunge her into the depths of Hell to burn for eternity.
Raimi wrote Drag Me to Hell with his brother before working
on the Spider-Man film trilogy (2002–2007).
The film premiered at the Cannes Film Festival and was a critical and commercial
success, grossing $90.8 million worldwide against a $30 million budget.
It won the Saturn Award for Best Horror Film at the 36th Saturn Awards.
The film explores themes of work, gypsy, gore, curse, psychologist.
The tone is dark and intense.